Ò×¿¼·¶ÎÄÊ®¾Å
In the above picture, unaware of a stone in front of him,
a man stumbles over it and falls to the ground.
On the side of the picture,
several words stand prominent¡ªface the frustrations.
As far as I am concerned,
the painter means to remind us that we will unavoidably encounter setbacks,
which are represented by the stone in the picture,
and the best coping way is to confront and remove them.
Life is full of challenges and difficulties to every individual.
Some people with a strong will can withstand the test of adversities,
while others who are not ready for the battle against plight do nothing but surrender.
Take college students for example.
In addition to increased competition in the job market,
complicated personal relationships and high expectations from parents
have imposed on them an invisible pressure and anxiety.
A few students are so overwhelmed by pessimism that they put an end to their young lives.
What a pity!
They could have avoided the tragedy if they had mustered up their courage to face
and overcome these seemingly insurmountable hardships.
We grow more mature by learning how to handle difficulties.
And only the mature and unyielding people will survive in the harsh reality.